<resources>
    <string name="help_sms_content_filter">
        <![CDATA[
        These rules apply to the text content of SMS, MMS, or notifications.<br>
        <br>
        <title><b> - Some typical patterns</b></title>:<br>
        &ensp; - Contains \"verification\": <highlight><b>.*verification.*</b></highlight><br>
        &ensp; - Contains any of the words: <highlight><b>.*(police|hospital|verification).*</b></highlight>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="help_quick_copy">
        <![CDATA[
        A quick way to copy content from SMS messages or phone numbers, making it easy to grab verification codes or incoming numbers.<br>
        <br>
        When it matches, a button like <title><b>Copy: 123456</b></title> will appear in the notification.<br>
        <br>
        A sample rule for extracting verification codes:<br>
        &emsp; Using capturing group:<br>
        &emsp;&emsp; <highlight><b>code.*?(\\d+) </b></highlight><br>
        &emsp; Another approach using lookaround:<br>
        &emsp;&emsp; <highlight><b>(?&lt;=code.{0,3})\\d+</b></highlight>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="help_apply_to_call_sms">
        <![CDATA[
        Choose which of Calls, SMS, MMS, Notification Title, and Notification Body this rule applies to.<br>
        Uncheck all of them to disable the rule without deleting it.
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="help_apply_to_number_and_message">
        <![CDATA[
        When <title><b>Number</b></title> is checked, this rule will extract content from the incoming number.
        For example, use <b>(.*)</b> to copy the phone number.<br>
        <br>
        When <title><b>Content</b></title> is checked, this rule will extract content from the SMS message body,
        such as verification codes.
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="help_apply_to_passed_and_blocked">
        <![CDATA[
        When <highlight><b>Passed</b></highlight> is checked, this rule will apply to passed calls and messages.<br>
        <br>
        When <error><b>Blocked</b></error> is checked, this rule will apply to blocked calls and messages.
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="title_rule_testing">Rule Testing</string>
    <string name="help_test_rules">
        <![CDATA[
        This helps to check if the rules are set as expected. It is just a simulation and will
          not actually pop up an incoming call, text message, or notification. <br>
        <br>
        <title><b>Call</b></title><br>
        <b>Phone Number</b> and <b>Caller Name</b> are tested against Basic Rules, Number Rules,
          and Content Rules that apply to calls. <br>
        <br>
        <title><b>SMS</b></title><br>
        <b>Phone Number</b> and <b>SMS Content</b> are tested against Basic Rules, Number Rules,
          and Content Rules that apply to SMS/MMS. <br>
        <br>
        <title><b>Notification</b></title><br>
        <b>Phone Number</b> is tested against Basic Rules and Number Rules, same as a call/SMS.
          <b>Title</b> and <b>Body</b> are each tested independently against Number/Text Rules
          with Title/Body enabled under Apply to Notifications. <br>
        <br>
        The result is shown here, in the history log, and in notifications.
        ]]>
    </string>

</resources>